

# Mariia Shchepeleva

Full Stack Web Developer

aerocodepro@gmail.com

+380507545318

My name is Maria, and I am from Mykolaiv, Ukraine.

I have more than 9 years of experience in developing and customizing professional websites in WordPress. I also worked with Joomla!, Prestashop, and other CMS.

Generally I work as Full Stack developer and designer - I lead a project starting from learning the client's needs, then creating design prototype and finally creating a custom website and installing it to the client's server. I can also work as a lead of a small team when some of these work steps are performed by someone else.

### My skills

### Web Development:

- ✓ WordPress themes development and customization;
- ✓ WordPress extensions ACF, WooCommerce, LearnPress, Event Manager. I can create a customized shop or a learning system
- ✓ responsive HTML/SCSS coding using modern practices.
- √ performance optimization;
- ✓ bug fixing;

#### Design:

- √ Figma;
- ✓ Adobe Photoshop;
- ✓ Adobe Illustrator;

## **Work Experience**

Web Developer

Templatemonster.com

May 2012 - October 2015

I worked in the template customization department and was one of those who make various adjustments according to the client's needs - starting from changing color scheme and ending with adding custom functionality or moving the website to another engine.

**Full Stack** 

AeroCode.pro

2015 - Present time

AeroCode is a brand I created to showcase my portfolio. Here I work mostly as freelancer for my new and returning clients, making websites from scratch - exploring client's needs, creating designs and then creating custom themes in WordPress. I also provide support and teaching for clients, so they could manage their websites.

**Education** 

**Admiral Makarov National University of Shipbuilding** 

**Applied Linguistics** 

Specialist

2006-2011

**Interests** 

In my free time I teach social dancing (kizomba and bachata) and work as a manager of a local social dance school.

Languages

✓ English: fluent

✓ Russian: native

✓ Ukrainian: fluent

√ German: basic

**Portfolio** 

√ http://salsa-club.in.ua/

√ http://aerocode.pro/

√ http://redpointsales.ru/

√ https://ksenita.com

√ https://priroda.kiev.ua/

- ✓ http://floweb.ch/
- ✓ https://www.b-public.ch/
- √ https://www.rube-immobilien.ch/
- √ https://babyfeeling.at/
- ✓ https://weloveaccounting.de/
- ✓ https://www.berger-gartenbau.ch/
- √ https://www.stereotactic.org/
- ✓ https://ueberbrueckungshilfe-beantragen.de/
- ✓ https://prometheus.org.ua/
- ✓ https://feelfood.ca/

Most of these websites were created with my design and coding, some of them – with design provided by a customer. You can read more in <a href="https://aerocode.pro">https://aerocode.pro</a>.